Your website should do more than just tell
people you exist.
It should help the right customer
understand your offer,
explain the next steps of what they need
to do in order to book
with you, and then also hear back from
your business all while
they are still interested.
At Aurex Business Labs, we build revenue
website systems for established
businesses in North Mississippi.
That means a completely custom website
with clear messaging,
focused conversion paths, lead tracking,
a CRM system, and automated follow-up.
Here's what it looks like. Someone finds
your business on Google.
They understand what you do and then
request a quote.
That inquiry goes into your business's
CRM.
An automated response from your business
is triggered and sent
to that lead.
And the original traffic source stays
connected with that opportunity
in your CRM so that you can track where
all your customers are
actually coming from.
Our projects start at $3,500 with $1,750
being the deposit,
and then the other $1,750 paid once you
have approved and are
completely happy with your website and
complete setup.
And we put $1,000 on our launch
commitment,
which just means that if we did not
complete the project within
21 days after getting all of the assets
from you and everything,
and it's on us, we will actually pay you
$1,000 back from the
website build.
So that's how much that we guarantee that
we will get this done
in 21 days or less.
To start, I will go ahead and book your
website revenue review.
We will look at your current website,
your path to inquiry, your offer,
your tracking, and your follow-up.
You'll leave the call with a better
understanding of what needs
to happen next for your business and also
whether this is the
correct system for you and your business.
So, click the button below and schedule
your free review now.